nimblestorage.com 2018-02-02

# Privacy | HPE™

Personal information is any information that personally identifies you or from which you could be identified.  This may include your name, address, telephone number, email address and profession or occupation.

HPE collects, exports, and uses personal information to manage your relationship with HPE and better serve you by personalizing your experience and interaction with HPE. Such collection is done with appropriate notice and consent, along with required filings with data protection authorities, where required.

HPE may collect your personal information through your access and use of website,  web-based applications, or mobile applications, during conversations or correspondence with HPE representatives, when you purchase goods or services or complete an online application form.

HPE may collect personal information from you in connection with:

  * product or service orders, activations, and registrations
  * profile creation and user verification for online services
  * information requests or complaints
  * marketing, newsletter or support subscriptions
  * contest entries or survey participation
  * instant credit applications
  * job applications
  * event registration
  * visits or browsing on HPE websites

The types of personal information HPE may collect from you includes:

  * personal and business contact information, such as name, address, telephone number, and email address
  * in some cases, your business contact data may be provided to HPE by a designated entity within your business or enterprise (such as a member of your IT department)
  * financial information, such as your credit/debit card number or other billing information
  * other unique information such as user IDs and passwords, product functionality, product and service preferences, contact preferences, educational and employment background, and job interest data
  * geo-location data such as your IP address or physical location when you request location based services
  * details of the products and services you have purchased from us or which you have enquired about, together with any additional information necessary to deliver those products and services and to respond to your enquiries
  * any additional information relating to you that you provide to us directly through our websites or indirectly through use of our websites or online presence, through our representatives or otherwise
  * information you provide to us through our service center, customer surveys or visits by our representatives from time to time

If you apply for instant credit, we may ask you to provide additional personal information such as salary, government issued identification number, banking/financial account information, and other information  (for example from credit reporting agencies) to authenticate you and verify credit worthiness. This information will be used by our financial services providers in determining whether to extend you credit and how much to extend.

If you post, comment, indicate interest or complaint, or share personal information, including photographs, to any public forum on an HPE site, social network, blog, or other such forum, please be aware that any information you submit can be read, viewed, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to contact you, send you unsolicited messages, or for purposes that neither you nor HPE have control over. HPE is not responsible for the personal information you choose to provide in these forums.

In addition to the information you provide, HPE may also collect information during your visit to an HPE website, web-based application, or a website “powered by” another company on behalf of HPE, through our Automatic Data Collection Tools, which include Web beacons, cookies, and similar technologies, as well as embedded Web links. These tools collect certain traffic information that your browser sends to a website, such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, unique device identifier, clickstream behavior (i.e., the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with HPE websites or “powered by” websites) and product information. HPE may also use some of these Automatic Data Collection Tools in connection with certain emails and communications sent from HPE and therefore may collect information using these tools when you open the email or click on a link contained in the email. To learn more, read How HPE uses automatic data collection tools.

HPE also collects information from publicly or commercially available sources that it deems credible. Such information may include your name, address, email address, preferences, interests, and demographic/profile data. The information HPE collects from its public or commercial sources may be used along with the information HPE collects when you visit HPE’s sites. For example, HPE may compare the geographic information acquired from commercial sources with the IP address collected by Automatic Data Collection Tools to derive your general geographic area.

Where necessary, HPE may also use information provided by you or your employer, together with information from publicly available and other online and offline sources, to conduct due diligence checks on business contacts as part of HPE’s anti-corruption program.

HPE may also collect some information that is not personal information because it does not identify you or anyone else.  For example, we may collect anonymous answers to surveys or aggregated information about how users use our websites, products or services.
